[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":94285,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":3061524,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":7998,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":3069527,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":11740,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":3081272,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":5036,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":3086322,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":5555,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":3091883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1758,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":3093643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the  second  one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":19402,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":3113047,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1795,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":3114844,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6380,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":3121227,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1655,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":3122884,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":5467,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":3128353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Corre ct! 3 +< sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1415,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":3129771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4474,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":3134246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1415,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":3135662,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6 </sub> 3 ? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3599,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":3139265,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1777,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":3141045,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract  6 to get  your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3822,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":3144869,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1416,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":3146288,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4475,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":3150764,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1381,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":3152146,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3487,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":3155635,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1922,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":3157560,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":16432,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":3174000,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Sim ilarly,  3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":29612,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":3203615,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":22301,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":3225919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4873,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":3230796,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What  is the i nverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4516,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":3235314,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1341,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":3236657,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":5093,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":3241752,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1451,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":3243206,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3193,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":3246401,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because  2 +<sub >6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1523,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":3247925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3865,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":3251791,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5124,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":3256918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to success ively ap ply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":48217,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":3305137,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2  +<sub>6< /sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":64374,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":3369513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":6971,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":3376499,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2705,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":3379207,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":" Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":6266,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":3385476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":16820,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":3402298,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.10-0 "},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":6977,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":3409278,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":18238,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":3427517,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No ","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":5657,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":3433177,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":4950,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":3438128,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /> <br />We 'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":18470,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":3456601,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4919,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":3461522,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":2058,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":3463582,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4735,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":3468318,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":3473928,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3613,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":3477544,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":5570,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":3483116,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4602,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":3487722,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":13340,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":3501064,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"I got 5 because 4+1 is 5, which is not greater than 9.","explanation_history":["I got 4 b","I got 4 ","I got 4","I got 5 bea","I got 5 because the","I got 5 because th","I got 5 because t","I got 5 because 4_1","I got 5 because 4_","I got 5 because 4 added b","I got 5 because 4+1 is 5, which is not greater than 0","I got 5 because 4+1 is 5, which is not greater than 9."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":47046,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":3548113,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8+4 is 12,  this is  greater than 9, so we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3.","explanation_history":["*+4","*+","*","8+4 is 12 w","8+4 is 12 ","8+4 is 12, this is greater than 9, so we subrt","8+4 is 12, this is greater than 9, so we subr","8+4 is 12, this is greater than 9, so we subtract 9 from 12 to get 2","8+4 is 12, this is greater than 9, so we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":38319,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":3586435,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"We do not add anything to get 9 from 9.","explanation_history":["We do not add anything to get 9 from 9."],"response_history":["0"],"rt":30278,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":3616717,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12- 0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":13945,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":3630679,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":4933,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":3635614,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4261,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":3639879,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"We need to add 6 to 3 in order to make 9.","explanation_history":["We need to add 6 to 4","We need to add 6 to 3 in order to make 9."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":20179,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":3660060,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"It is not possible to get all solutions from 2, we cannot get 1, 3, 5, etc.","explanation_history":["It is not possible to get all solutions from 2, we cannot get 1, e,","It is not pos sible to  get all solutions from 2, we cannot get 1, e","It is not possible to get all solutions from 2, we cannot get 1, 3, t","It is not possible to get all solutions from 2, we cannot get 1, 3, 5, etc","It is not possible to get all solutions from 2, we cannot get 1, 3, 5, etc."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":33794,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":3693855,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"We are able to gain all solutions from 3.","explanation_history":["We at","We are ablt ","We are ablt","We are able to gain all solutions for","We are able to gain all solutions fo","We are able to gain all solutions from 2","We are able to gain all solutions from 3."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":17273,"trial_type":"question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":3711130,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"It is not possible to get all solutions from 5.","explanation_history":["It is not possible to get all solutions from 3","It is not possible to get all solutions from 5."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":17209,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":3728341,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"It is possible to get the solutions from 6.","explanation_history":["We can get solutions ","We can get solutions"," It is po sso","It is possible to get the solutions feo","It is possible to get the solutions fe","It is possible to get the solutions from t","It is possible to get the solutions from 5","It is possible to get the solutions from 6."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":33441,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":3761787,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":16295,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":3778091,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"The formula is +n","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["The fr","The formula is +n"],"rt":34389,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":3812485,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x=+n","explain":true,"explanation":"Any number can be plugged into n.","explanation_history":["Any number can be plugged into n."],"response_history":["x+","x=+n"],"rt":45977,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":3858464,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"fr ee","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"If it can be equal to 1.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["If it can be equal to 1."],"rt":17596,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":3876064,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":8365,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":3884439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":11031,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":3895473,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":8953,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":3904428,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"x can be further divided until it can be evenly divided  by n.","explanation_history":["x can be further dici","x can be further dic","x can be further divided until it can be evenly divided by n."],"response_history":["True"],"rt":29318,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":3933749,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":29135,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":3962887,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"mu lti","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Always","explain":true,"explanation":"It is equal to 1. Do not know answer.","explanation_history":["It is w","It is ewaul to","It is ewaul t","It is ewaul ","It is ewaul","It is ewau","It is ewa","It is ew","It is eqial t","It is eqial ","It is eqial","It is eqia","It is eqi","It is equal to 1 so it ","It is equal to 1 ","It is equal to 1. Do not know anse","It is equal to 1. Do not know answer."],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":80599,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":4043494,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":86447,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":4129958,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2216,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":4132181,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"24","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["24"],"rt":6467,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":4138651,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degr ee","Doc torate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some graduate school, no degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Some graduate school, no degree"],"rt":4609,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":4143263,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Calculus ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Calculus "],"rt":21965,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":4165233,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it  was","3  - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":45892,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":4211127,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5 - used it, remember and understand it","4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":13399,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":4224528,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4192,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":4228723,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3403,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":4232129,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did y ou enjoy  this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3007,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":4235139,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":3303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":4238444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":6204,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":4244651,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4655,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":4249307,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Interesting HIT!","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Interesting HIT!"],"rt":6511,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":4255820,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]